and I don't know exactly where I'm at
but with my experiments but it's a
significant number up there as well that
the minerals that you start with stay in
suspension but as the longer you run the
look there are minerals that builds are
there they're deposits built up at the
bottom of a geocell or my device that
get thicker and thicker even though the
original fluid still has all the mineral
the original mineral level in it so you
take that off and and put more water
back into it and you just keep on
building up building up the elements and
the longer you do this the more you can
multiply it so I haven't found a limit
yet but mighty experiments as my
experimenting is very very new I started
this this year thinking that I was going
to give a lecture strictly about the
different uses of hydrogen and fuels
fuel supply heating and cooking and
waste remediation and then in the
process have this discovery and realized
this is really really important and
needs to get to people so I I changed my
presentation significantly and and
brought this here that's why it's it's a
it's an emerging technology and it's
it's something new that people can
experiment with but I felt like it was
really important so that's why that's
why I brought it here to present you
have some associates you talked about
some other people the 13 fold increase
how many people do you know who have
been able to replicate this doing this
on purpose there aren't very many people
I'm sure that there are a lot of people
that have discovered this on accident
but but doing this on purpose no there's
people there are actually we're actually
into the borderline alchemical field
which I've seen some amazing amazing
things this last year and they do create
elements all the time they just don't
talk about it and they have a they have
a different system of of the different
system that we were using here but it is
it is reality
historically you talked about the onus
domain name alchemical hydrogen dot-com
and you've had that domain for quite
some time and yet this particular aspect
is a new discovery what was our chemical
hydrogen before this discovery um I was
using well I still use hydrogen to
alchemically destroy waste products and
I was using hydrogen to in internal
combustion engines to eliminate the
exhaust and the the VOCs and the
unburned hydrocarbons to keep people
from being exposed to that as well as
just having the engines run cleaner and
I use the word alchemical hydrogen
because we're getting into strange field
but my life I was led to study alchemy
and I learned about the I studied all
the ancient techniques of alchemy to not
only create elements but purify the
human body and and expend and and clean
out the consciousness per se and then I
was led to apply that are see me then I
was led to to develop hydrogen
technology then I married the two
together which is that's why I called it
alchemical hydrogen because I was using
and alchemical fluids in the production
of hydrogen to get
really phenomenal hydrogen and there's
there's many types of Browns gas and
that some is high purity some is low
purity and the different purity levels
have different uses so if you have
really high purity you can vaporize
anything and you can destroy tungsten
and you can you can remediate radiation
and such and but you can't do that with
with a low level of Browns gas you can't
do it with a low energy but the low
energy Browns gas has different uses you
can use it for cookie you can use it for
you can use it for different
applications applications that you
couldn't use the super powerful
vaporizing and imploding a level of
Browns gas so by applying now chemical
fluid to this I could get high-level
Browns gas without the conventional a
lot of without the conventional
resonance and the electrical circuits
and stuff like that I could generate the
the high level Browns gas without using
the expensive equipment or I could vary
the levels of the fluids and get the low
level Browns gas that I could use for
other processes so that's why I called
it all chemical hydrogen because I was
using this fluid in different locations
and such so that's where that's where
the name came from ok well I think it's
poor too--it is that you grab that
domain name and now you have this
totally new process that I think fits
the name even better than she said
absolutely
except it's not just hydrogen as
hydrogen and oxygen from a Browns gas
process but Hyder I mean that that's a
good name still it is it is we actually
there's actually four times the amount
of oxygen than there is hydrogen so well
four times the volume excuse me or but
yes it is four to is
rather than happen in terms of rolling
this out into a practical application
where people can actually do this on a
commercial scale how close do you think
you are or someone could be that you you
could you know and you're willing to
train people you're willing to somebody
comes along say hey could you show me
how to do this you glad to do it
and you're very sharing that way it's
really quite phenomenal I would plug in
here though something I don't think
Vernon would say that if he does help
you make sure you remember him in any
kind of you know revenue that you're
making on this that you you know
volunteer some kind of a royalty that
goes back to him to help his research
because this is just one of many things
that he's playing with he's extremely
prolific as an inventor and an intuitive
in the scientific field and so I think
he deserves that kind of sustainment but
answer the question of how close and
what would it take to there's obviously
a whole whole bunch of different
applications of this but what would be
the low-hanging fruit and how hard would
it be or easy would it be to get to that
low-hanging fruit well the the easiest
way to go about this would be to have to
just create a little device and these
things could go into a five-gallon
bucket if you wanted to be really
low-tech and put it together or like I
do I use the
the heavy do these see PVC plastic and
stainless steel but the easiest way to
do this which means to just build the
device and hook it up to a solar panel
and start dropping out the elements and
finding an Avenue you could sell it or
or use the elements in some in some way
so I'm very I'm very much into people
being self-sufficient so let's say you
Stirling wanted to want to set this up
at your house and you could start
generating power and you've got a little
shed in the backyard hooked up to and
you've got solar power mounted on it and
you just be using the Sun using a
passive energy source to to develop a
monetize stream okay let's just say that
and so you have that set up at your
place and your neighbor can have one set
up to actually put it into a production
level I I'm not a huge fan of big
corporations getting control of things
and they don't like to have anything
that they don't you know have an
iron-fisted control over so but if you
had a group of people that could put it
into production
you'd have you know a piece of property
with with a bunch of solar panels set up
and a bunch of hydrogen devices there
that are just you know generating the
generating the elements and generating a
usable energy source so that's that's
the the probably the fastest way and the
easiest way to start to move this into
the move this into the the production
level that you talked about
you were talking about taking a chemical
type of element a molecule that you had
developed and you found it's showing up
in large quantities and that was an
indicator to you that something was
happening
reproduction Weiser alchemical wise how
hard would it be to isolate these things
once you've created them well it's just
a matter of on an individual level it'd
be a matter of some chemistry I have a
friend that takes our alchemical gold
and uses a little using a little bit of
chemistry process on it and creates gold
chloride which he then sells to a
chemical company gold chloride is an
industrial it's it's what we call
precious chemical if you're working with
precious metals for to actually create a
revenue stream it's it's easier to work
with precious chemicals rather than
precious metals because they're at least
four times more expensive than the
metals so if you're working with gold
chloride it's not sixteen hundred
dollars an ounce it's in the
neighborhood of its neighborhood of six
thousand dollars for a high-profile
house for high purity gold chloride and
it's funny because the process of
dropping gold out from a mint from a
mining process you go through the gold
chloride stage and then you go into the
yellow metal and everybody wants the
yellow metal but that's gold fever if
you stick with the gold chloride you can
have a completely different a completely
different level of monetary income same
thing with silver Silver's I don't let's
say silver was $10 an ounce silver
nitrate are some of the different
precious chemicals from silver actually
are four times that amount four to ten
times that amount is if you if you can
create the right type
then people sell that chemist sell that
and and make a significant amount of
money more than the more than the metal
itself so the process of dropping out
developments would be to find the proper
proper place to to to move it and that
would involve a little bit of chemistry
and selling it to to chemist shop or you
could use some thought of this before
you could use an electroplating process
and plate this metal onto a onto a
substrate and then just sell that and
there wouldn't be chemistry involved at
all so there's different ways not being
a not be an actual chemist I have died I
haven't explored all those options just
been really busy you know working with
the technology so the people turning
this into a cottage industry could find
a local substance it's expensive that
they could implement into this process
to replicate it and and sell it locally
we're suffering from a huge people don't
know about it very much yet but we're
actually suffering from a huge
deficiency and in the rare earths right
now rare earths are very important for
the for the rare of course rare earth
magnets but also the batteries that are
being developed and the blooms are
horrible exactly and so if you can
create a stream of the rare earths those
elements then you'd be sitting pretty
well now it would actually be a much
better way to go than worrying about the
worrying about the the elements gold and
such because from an al chemicals
perspective I have to throw this out
there
an alchemist is forbidden from making a
profit with gold they can use it to
further their research they can use it
to keep themselves alive but if they try
to elevate their status in life with
gold they moving but they don't some of
them die some of them
are severely punished by the universe so
it's like a spiritual calling so to
speak to be an alchemist absolutely you
have you can't be in it for Greek you
can't be in it for control or
manipulating if you if your motives are
pure then you can be an alchemist so
it's a warning about getting into
alchemy that you have to be a good
person and stay that way absolutely
absolutely now let's talk I could
actually talk you more about that but
that gets really esoteric but I have
seen some things this last year what
about let's talk about what kind of
process you would be in looking at to
get set up just first of all to
replicate it to prove to yourself that
this is real how many what's expensive
materials in time to replicate and to
see that the effect does work well first
thing is you start out with stainless
steel plates 316 I always work with 316
stainless there are other materials and
different things you can play with but
the most readily available 316 stainless
and I like 6x6 squares but whatever
you're working with whatever size the
material vessel you're working with so I
use eight and a half inch well 8 inch
nominal see PVC pipe and seal it closed
with these things inside me so 6x6 works
pretty well for that and you have these
here with you at the conference maybe
what we could do is after this episode
we could have you actually pull it apart
and show us the different components and
it could we do that that off and and put
more water back into it and you just
keep on building up building up the
elements and the longer you do this the
more you can mold
plants so I haven't found a limit yet
but my experiment as my experimenting is
very very new
I started this this year thinking that I
was going to give a lecture strictly
about the different uses of hydrogen and
fuels fuel supply heating and cooking
and and I don't know exactly where I'm
at but with with my experiments but it's
a significant number of there as well
that the minerals that you start with
stay in suspension but as the longer you
run the look there are minerals that
Bilt's are there there deposits built up
at the bottom of a geocell or my device
that get thicker and thicker even though
the original fluid still has all the
mineral the original mineral level in it
so you take how many people do you know
who have been able to replicate this
doing this on purpose there aren't very
many people I'm sure that there are a
lot of people that have discovered this
on accident but but doing this on
purpose no there's there are actually
we're actually into the borderline
alchemical field which I've seen some
amazing amazing things this last year
and they do create elements all the time
they just don't talk about it and they
have a they have a different system of
of the very different system that we
were using here but it is it is reality
historically you talked about
yonas domain-name alchemical hydrogen
calm and you've had that domain for
quite some time and yet this particular
aspect is a new discovery well waste for
mediation and then in the process have
this discovery and realized this is
really really important and needs to get
to people so I I changed my presentation
significantly and
and brought this here that's why it's
it's a it's an emerging technology and
it's it's something new that people can
experiment with but I felt like it was
really important so that's why that's
why I brought it here to present you
have some associates you talked about
some other people the 13 fold increase